their husbands give them cards, that is, well, they
мужья им карты дают то есть ну деньги
give them money, cards that they earn there
дают карты которые они зарабатывают там
and just go out with this money, just
и просто на эти деньги гуляют просто
go out, clubs there, restaurants, go
гуляет клубы там рестораны ходят куда
anywhere with this money, that is, I
угодно на эти деньги то есть я правильно
understand correctly that the husband is fighting with his card, the
понимаю что муж воюет на сво карту берёт
wife takes this and goes out with this one  map in the
жена и это и гуляет на эту карту в
clubs there jaga-jaga yes
клубах там джага-джага да
My name is
Меня зовут
Irakli nya
Иракли ня
Robert nice I am from Kutasi Georgia And
Роберт приятно Я из кутаси Грузии А
you are from Moscow and who is
вы с Москвы а кто по
Armenian by nationality Armenian I see that
национальности армян армени вижу что
you are celebrating Armenian Independence Day today Yes
тебя сегодня День независимости
no No no idle you are more Russian
Да не Нет не празд ты больше русский уже
than Armenian yes Well
чем армянин да
yes  betrayed his
Ну да предал свой
family Why
род Почему
betrayed And what about Georgia I’m from Georgia from
предал А ты что с грузие я с Грузии с
Kuta those Ukraine stands and I put VN I talked with the
Кута те Украина стоит а я VN ставил я с
Ukrainians for an hour
украинцами час
and why are they and because if
общался а для чего те а потому что если
I’m from Georgia Yes then they don’t want to communicate with me,
я из Грузии Да они тогда со мно не хотят
leave either Russia or
общаться оставить либо Россия либо
Ukraine because they either talk to their own people
Украина потому что они Либо со своими
or to the Russians. I left Georgia and spilled
говорят либо с русскими Я оставил Грузию
water. Why don’t they
пролию по А почему с грузины ми не
communicate with the Georgians? I don’t
общаются не
know what it is they say, that we are for
знаю что такого они говорят что мы за
Russia and
Россию и
that’s all. Well, they communicate with Russians very poorly,
всё Ну они с русскими очень плохо
communication here is bad, of course. And
общаются общение тут плохое конечно А я
when I left  I went out and installed a Russian
когда выходил Я выходил ставил русский
VPN so they were yelling at me,
ВПН так они орали на меня просто
it’s just brutal, it’s just that they’re not yelling at me either,
жесть это просто да не они на меня тоже
but I don’t react to it.
орут но я не реагирую на это
And what do you think, like why did you attack
А а ты как считаешь типа зачем вы напали
Ukraine? I don’t think anything at all.
Украину я вообще ничего не
Count to
считаю Посчитай до
children. Well, who are you for?  for the Russians or for the
дети Ну ты за кого за Русских или за
Ukraine I mean what to be for the Russians the Russians
Украину я что что быть за русских русски
can be let’s
могут быть
say you’re for Ukraine And why
вот допустим ты за Украину А почему Вот
You have a point of view Why are you for
есть же у тебя точка зрения Почему ты за
Ukraine and not for Russia precisely because
Украину а не за Россию именно потому что
I’m
я
not Russia attacked Ukraine Russia
не Россия напала на Украину Россия
attacked
напала на
Georgia for  Russia Only there may
Грузию за Россию Только могут
be a base Russia Russia didn’t attack
быть база Россия Россия не нападала же
Georgia, it seems like it didn’t
на Грузию вроде как не
attack And when was the last time it attacked in 2008? Yes,
нападала А когда нападал он в 2008
Russian troops are stationed on the territory of the occupied
российские на территории оккупированной
part of the region in Chab and Abkhazia itself.
части региона сама чаб и Абхазии
Why do you even need this
стоят А тебе вообще для чего эта
policy
политика
because Russia occupied
нужна потому что Россия оккупировала
part of my territory,
часть моей территории
Georgia, because of this, yes, yes, it attacked
Грузии из-за этого да да напала на
Ukraine, also Russia is attacking
Украину также Россия нападает на
everyone. Well, what are you going to do? You have to
всех Ну что сделаешь
pour out Russia, and
сдела лить Россию надо вот и
it won’t work out. Why won’t it work out there? There are
всё не получится Почему не получится там
almost no Russians there; they’re all
уже ж русских почти даже нет там всё
Armenians, Azerbaijanis, Georgians, our type,
армяне азербайджанцы грузины наши типа
Chechens, Dagestanis, Russians  there’s already a
чеченцы дагестанцы русские уже там
shorter nation there, soon damn Russia will be
короче нация там скоро блин Россию ту
divided into clans in the territory and everything
поделят на кланы на территории и всё
will be fine Well, that’s understandable, but there are
будет нормально Ну это понятно но
still more Russians in Russia, and
русских же всё равно больше в России а
how many Russian children are there in families?
сколько сколько в семьях Русских детей
I don’t know, I didn’t let down the statistics.
Я не знаю я статистику не подводил
Maxim has one maximum And at 40 years old  or at
Максиму один максимум И в 40 лет или в
they give birth Yes, in general, now Russians don’t
рожают Да вообще сейчас русские не
give birth practically, that’s all. That’s why in 10
рожают практически вот и всё Поэтому 10
years there won’t be any Russians anymore, and the Chechens of the
лет и русских уже не будет а чеченцы
Caucasus are all multiplying. The Caucasus is
Кавказ весь размножается Кавказ
handsome
красавчики потому
because Nita Nita I don’t have a lot of money because of this they
что нита нита Нелю денег изза этого они
multiply. And vice versa. I mean, they don’t
размножаются Вот и наоборот В смысле не
multiply, on the contrary, look at what they are  They don’t
размножают наоборот посмотри что они не
reproduce not because of poverty, they
размножаются не из-за нищеты они
reproduce because
размножаются потому что
they And the theory says that
они А теория Да на гласит что не
many people don’t reproduce because they do
размножаются у многих потому что денег
n’t have money. It’s just that they have to support children, and the
нету Просто детей содержать вот и всё
opposite is true; they reproduce in
наоборот как раз размножаются в
Russia. Well, yes. How is it that in
России Ну да А как так получается что в
Russia there is no money there?  gold oil
России нету денег там золото нефть
Diamond people don’t have money to
Алмаза у людей нет денег чтобы
reproduce
размножаться
Well, I’m talking about the general population, I’m
Ну я говорю про общее население я сейчас
not talking about myself now Well yes, but the general
не про себя не говорю Ну да но общее
population Like you I just live in
население Как у вас Я просто живу в
Georgia and not in Russia How is it that
Грузии а не в России Как так получается
in Russia gold oil diamonds is the
что в России золото нефть алмазы
richest country  people don’t have money
богатейшая страна у людей нет денег
to
чтобы
reproduce Yes, I
размножаться Да я
know Well, how do you think you live,
знает Ну как ты думаешь ты живёшь ты
how long have you been living in Russia
сколько живёшь в России
already T 15 somewhere already, well, 15 years already I should be
уже Т 15 гдето уже ну 15 лет уже должен
singing like how is it possible that such a
поть типа как так получается что такая
rich country and a
богатейшая страна а
poor one? Yes, I really care about other people
бедная Да я на других людей на самом
A  What country are you a citizen of?
деле А ты гражданин какой
Russian citizen My
страны гражданин России У меня
citizenship is Russian Cool And you do
гражданство Российское Прикольно И тебе
n’t care about Russia Well
пофиг на Россию Ну да тоже
yes, that’s cool too, but what will I do? Well,
прикольно ну а что я что сделаю Ну
every person lives the way he needs to,
каждый человек живёт как ему надо
well.
хорошо
How do you feel about the fact that a bunch of
Как как ты относишься к тому что куча
Russians are dying in Ukraine Now why do
россиян умирает в Украине Сейчас зачем
you need it?  Well, for money after money, many people go
вам Ну за бабки за бабками многи едут не
wrong in your country, if in your country
так вам в стране если в вашей стране
Russia, why is
России зачем
this a universal
это универсальный
allotment for
отве льный
you to answer What should I tell you or
тебе отвечать Что мне тебе что ли или
what if I don’t know the answer what will I
что если я не знаю ответа что я тебе
answer you And who do you
отвечу А ты кем
work for? And I sell things at the market
работаешь А я на рынке продаю вещи свой
I have my own point. I sell things there, I
своя точка есть у меня Я там вещи продаю
understand sales
понял продаж
are fine, it turns out fine, I
нормально нормально выходит у меня там
understand how much it
понял сколько
turns out to be 1300 somewhere. Well, a month is normal
выходит 1300 где-то Ну месяц нормально
and the average salary in general is 50,000, wait,
а средняя зарплата вообще 50.000 подожди
am I correct, I understand correctly that while the
я правильно я правильно понимаю что пока
Russian Vanka is going for women in Ukraine You are
русский Ванька идёт за баб в Украину Ты
an Armenian  who came to Russia,
армянин который приехал в Россию
you earn money in the market, 3000
зарабатываешь бабки на рынке 3000
dollars,
долларов да
yes, many Armenians generally move a lot of
да многие армяне вообще двигаются много
money to
денег
earn damn it, it turns out I’m not
зарабатывать блин то получается я не
Russians in
русские в
Russia, in short, they don’t have money, but
России они короче не имеют денег а
Armenians in Russia have
армяне в России имеют
money Yes, they have money, gold whatever
деньги Да имеют деньги золото что
you want is good, but Natasha’s Russians,
хочешь хорошо а русские Наташи
then it turns out  Russians are dying there in
получается тогда русские там умирают в
Ukraine and they are not
Украине а их не
Natashas, ​​but handsome guys are hanging out with the Armenians.
Наташи да вот с армянами ходят
Well, what is
красавчики Ну а сдела
Russian
русский такой
like? Well, I
какой Ну вот я вот видео
watched a video on
смотрел на
YouTube and they asked that’s why you went
ютуберу го спросили Вот почему ты пошёл
to war. Yes, he says, I went to
Ну на войну Да он говорит я пошёл
defend
защищать
the Motherland, he went to defend the Motherland.  but he did
Родину он пошёл защищать Родину а он
n’t go to his homeland. His homeland is
пошёл не на свою родину Родина его Вот
here, this Land is his homeland. He went to
здесь эта Земля Вот его Родина он пошёл
defend his homeland in a foreign country. How to
защищать свою родину в чужую страну Как
understand this? Well, this is absurd.
это понять Ну это абсурд же Ну
Well, he died there too, and his Natasha,
да и там короче помер а его Наташа
in short, got seven lemons, bought a
короче получила сем лимонов купила
car, and he drives with  Armenian Yes, damn,
машину Да и ездит с армянином Да блин
this
вот эта
scheme is generally a
схема вообще
business, damn Yes, it’s
бизнес блин Да капец это
cool, it’s just not
прикольно просто яже не
Poma 7 million is that 7 million
Пома 7 млн это что там 7 млн квартиру
to buy an apartment and some kind of dead car to
купить и какую-нибудь дохлую машину
buy all this There’s not enough money for anything, it’s
купить всё это Денег ни на что не
cool, that is, it turns out that Putin is
прикольно то есть получается Путин
such a cool guy that  in short, he
настолько прикольный тип что он короче
divorced these Russians, they go there
развёл этих русских они едут туда
to die and then their wives
умирать а ихние жёны потом с армянами
have fun with the Armenians here yes Yes, it is
тут развлекаются да Да так есть это
true. Cool And who else besides Arm do the
правда Прикольно А с кем ещ кроме Арм
Russians have fun with when their
русские Девушки развлекаются когда их
husbands are there in
мужья там в
the Northern Fleet Well, the husbands give them cards, that is, well, they
СФ Ну мужья им карты дают то есть ну
give the cards money  that they
деньги дают карты которые они
earn there and just hang out with this money,
зарабатывают там и просто на эти деньги
just hang out in the clubs there, restaurants
гуляют просто гуляют клубы там рестораны
go anywhere with this money, that is,
ходят куда угодно на эти деньги то есть
I understand correctly that the husband fights on his
я правильно понимаю что муж воюет на сво
card, the wife takes it, and that’s what she walks on
карту берёт жена и это и гуляет на эту
in the clubs there, jaga-jaga,
карту в клубах там джага-джага да
listen to
слышишь
him  a card in the war, he needs a card with money,
ему карта на войне ему карта с деньгами
and the chicks in the club need a card Well,
а тёлки в клубе карта нужна Ну там
in any case, there’s no money there, no way, but it’s a
по-любому надо там без денег никак да
good scheme, damn it,
хорошая схема
I’m not even
блин капец Вот это блин я даже не вот
sure, let’s say they’ll give him a card, he’s
допустим вот допустим дадут карту он там
smart there, so what
умт ну и что
Degi Yes, and she  hanging out in clubs for a month is
Деги Да а она месяца в клубах
not 2 months somewhere Well, there’s 7
торчать не 2 месяца где-то Ну там же 7
million then they give you more How much does the wife
млн потом ещё дают Сколько сколько жена
get of a dead friend who’s dead can
получается погибшего свош нека может
go out in clubs with this money Well,
гулять в клубах на эти деньги Ну в
depending How much he
зависимости Сколько
spends Well, I don’t know the prices of your
тратит Ну вот я не знаю цены ваших
clubs Well, you can spend from 10  before you can
клубах Ну можно потратить от 10 до можно
spend it right away, well, how much
потратить сразу ну на сколько это
time is enough for her to
времени хватит ей
hang out? Well, a year, about a year, I understand,
потусить Ну год год примерно год понял
that is, she can move around in clubs for a year,
то есть она год Короче может движить в
and then you need to find a new husband.
клубах а потом надо найти нового мужа Да
Yes, yes, that’s how it works. It’s
да да вот так и работает Это причём даже
not even easy to find her while she’s hanging out in  cubes,
не просто найти она пока тусит в кубах
she should already be looking for a guy who can
она уже должна искать мужика которого
be sent to her place,
отправить на сво
but it’s
но
given that not everyone will all go to hell, she
дано не все все пойдут на изза дене
won’t be able to get
не сможет
divorced. How do these Russian Natashas
развести А как как эти русские Наташи
find guys who they can send
находят мужиков которых могут отправить
to their place, like, well, that’s it. Well, go out into the street.
на сво типа ну это ж Ну на улицу выйди
Well, you’re in Russia. If only you lived  If only you could go out into the street,
Ну ты в России Если бы жил бы на улицу
there’s
выйди там
plenty of it. And how does she know, like, a fool is not a
полно А как она знает типа дурак не
fool on the street, you just walk on the street,
дурак на улице просто идёшь на улице
you follow him? You see someone coming, he
идёшь его Видишь какой какой-то идёт вот
approaches him, he says, come on, come on,
к нему подходит знакомится говорит давай
you come here for me, the money, that’s all,
Ты пойдёшь сюда мне деньги вот всё так
first you have to marry him, it
это сначала жениться на нём надо
turns out  Yes, get married Well, there’s
получается ей Да жениться Ну там проблем
no problem Get married there Wait, do you have
нету Жениться там Подожди А у тебя есть
any friends who sent a guy like that
какие-то знакомые которые так мужика
to the
отправили на
front? I don’t have any personal acquaintances, but the
фронт нет лично знакомых нету но в
Internet is full of people
интернете полно так
saying that, it could be deceiving. I don’t believe
говорят это может обманывает Я не верю
that this can happen, no, this happens
что такое может быть нет такое вот
all the time, it’s
постоянно
cool.  tin
прикольно жесть
I know what it was there mom and
Я знаю что такое что было там мама и
wife are fighting for money there swash I
жена бьются за деньги там свош вот это
know this there is
знаю там
fighting Yes there are few people getting these 7
биться Да там мало кто получать эти 7
million there they don’t find the body they
миллионов там не находит тело же найти
need to find and if they find it reputed not to be a
надо а если найдут
person there is no money there is no problem
слыл не человека нету денег нет пробле
understand
поня
Many people  the tank exploded, let's say,
Многие же в танке взорвался допустим
burned out all the bodies, no money, no everything, he's
сгорел всё тела нету денег нету всё он
disappeared. What kind of money there won't give anything anymore,
пропал Какие бабки там уже ничего не
that is, it turns out she
дадут то есть получается она где-то
lost a year somewhere, it turns out, yes, because for now
потеряла год выходит да потому что пока
she will divorce the unknown, missing with a
с этим разведётся безвести пропавшим с
new one, get married, so she'll lose at least a year
новым женится так как минимум год
Yes,
потеряет Да
yes there  a lot of people are dying, missing,
да там же полно погибает людей безвести
and you have any Armenian friends who
а у тебя есть ка армяне знакомые которые
went to this war. No, I don’t know any of them
пошли на войну эту Нет вообще таких не
right. Handsome Armenians are better off
знаю правильно армяне красавчики лучше
trading in the market than going to die there
торговать на рынке чем идти умирать там
for
за
Putin, they pay 200,000, meaning 200,000
Путина там 200000 платят смысл 200.000
if I earn more here, not
если я здесь больше зарабатываю не с
rightly so  Russians they are
прально это русские они
there they have to go to earn money for the
там им приходится идти зарабатывать на
war Armenians Handsome I am Georgians Armenians
войну армяне Красавчики Я грузины армяне
We have always kind of kept the
Мы всегда типа держали короче
markets shorter 90% of Russians
рынки 90% русских -
are marginalized who only and
это маргиналы которые только и
more and more I can’t say anything they don’t
всё больше ничего не могу сказать
want to work they don’t want anything Yes
работать не хотят ничего не хотят Да
we need to work and not
надо надо работать а не
sit they are wrong  they do it in short,
сидеть они неправильно делают они короче
everyone sits there America America
там все сидят там Америка Америка им
owes them that way America works too, yes the
должна так Америка работает тоже да
Armenians work, the Poles work, the Estonians
армяне работают поляки Работают эстонцы
work, everyone works, all the limits, like they
Работают все работают все предели типа
just drink, yes, yes, what’s the problem?
только бухает да да я в чём проблема
You can also make money, no
Можно же тоже зарабатывать деньги их
one stops them from doing
никто не останавливает в
this, they themselves don’t want to
этом они сами не хотят
it’s simple Why is it so Well, what do you
этого просто А почему так Ну как ты
think? Well, I don’t know, the mentality is probably
думаешь Ну не знаю менталитет наверное
so Russian,
такой русский
but
а
how did it happen that they have such a
как как так получилось что у них такой
mentality Yes, I
менталитет получился Да я
know it’s universal
знает это универсальный
The answer is the same answer yes yes And you have
Ответ один и тот же ответ да да А у вас
a lot of Armenians in Moscow
много в Москве армян
now I don’t know  Well, it seems to me,
сейчас не знаю Ну мне кажется
yes,
да
probably 300,000 Maybe to
наверное 300.000 Может на
Moscow Well, a lot, a lot Well, there are
Москву Ну много очень много Ну там же в
Azerbaijanis in the mix there, there are Armenians there,
перемешку там азербайджанцы там армяне
there are Georgians, too, there are the Caucasus and another
там грузины тоже ны там Кавказ ещ другой
bunch of all sorts Yes, of course, I don’t
куча всяких Да русских конечно мало
meet many Russians, Russians, where have they all
встречаю русские куда все
gone? And what is not visible on the streets There are
делись А что на улицах не видно
no Russians There are  but more often, non-Russians
Русских нет Есть но чаще вот не русских
meet, not Russians anymore,
встречаются больше не
mostly I wonder where the
основном интересно куда делись
Russians went in the war, probably they are fighting in the war,
русские на войне наверное на войне воюют
I think so
я так
[music]
[музыка]
that is, it turns out, but
думаю то есть получается а девчонки
Russian girls meet Russians They don’t
русские встречаются русских Не
meet, but Russian girls
встречаются а русские девчонки
meet Yes, there are plenty of them And how they
встречаются Да да их полно А как они
climb like that  Hungry people like on the street that I
лазят такие Голодные типа по улице что
can’t understand, damn it, maybe they can come to
не могу понять блин может приехать в
Moscow to
Москву
hang out for you
потусить тебе
Yes, come, well, I think damn it, if there’s
Да приезжай ну я думаю блин если там
such a movement there I would, in short, set it on fire
такой движ Я бы короче поджигал
if
если
there are hungry people there Natasha And where there where there,
там голодных Наташе А куда там где там
for example, I haven’t been to Moscow before if in
например я в Москве не был раньше если в
what areas I need to go  go where there are a lot of these
какие районы надо ехать где там этих
hungry people Natasha, the
голодных Наташе
center of Moscow is full there Well, why don’t I
много центр Москвы там полно Ну а как не
come up
подъеду
there with your husband if you don’t directly
там у тебя муж сли как мне не пря
approach me and ask and
подходишь и спрашиваешь да
say this to the woman directly Well, do
к женщине такое сказать напрямую Ну это
n’t worry, this is Moscow, that is, in Moscow
же не грузи это Москва то есть в Москве
you can approach a woman and  look for nasty things
можно к женщине подойти и искать гадости
and in short, this is the norm Yes, he won’t
и короче это норма Да ничего ничего не
say anything It’s a common thing and that’s exactly what they
скажет Обычное дело и им как раз они
want, for someone to approach them, they have
хотят этого чтобы к ним подходили им
nothing to do, they have money, there’s nothing to do
делать нечего у них деньги есть делать
with it, but you
с а
don’t believe that this
походи не веришь что такое
works, I came up a couple of times looking for it Well, well,
работает я пару раз подходил ищё Ну как
well  you told her, well, like, let’s
Ну что ты сказал ей Ну ну типа Давай
get acquainted. She says, well, let’s get acquainted. She says, well, she
познакомимся Она говорит ну давай ну ей
was 30 years old, somewhere around 30 years old. And what are you
30 лет где-то было 30 лет А тебе сколько
now,
сейчас
23? You decided to take an experienced one for a ride, yes, yes, you decided to take an
23 ты опытную решил взять покатать да да
experienced one for a ride, and and who has money,
опытную решил и и у которой деньги есть
in short, why did you need her with money?
короче она Зачем тебе она с деньгами
chickpeas gone she has money now no
нут на ушёл у неё деньги есть теперь не
why do you need exactly what exactly were you looking for with the
зачем тебе именно что ты именно искал с
money or are you just saying it’s just random,
деньгами или просто говориш так попало
not just looking for more experience and everything
не просто по опытнее искал и всё
older is good And what did you say let’s get
постарше хорошо И что ты сказал
acquainted and she says Yes And then
познакомимся и она говорит Да А дальше
how did
как
it just talk, walk and you  just walked with
это просто общались гуляли и ты просто с
her Well,
ней
yes,
да
that is, you didn’t even just
пра То есть ты её не даже просто
walk her No, well, then we
погулял Нет ну за потом мы же не один
chatted more than once several times, I think maybe you’re
раз чали несколько раз я думаю может ты
some kind of damn I don’t know, damn I didn’t fry
какой-то блин не знаю блин не отжарил
it at all, you know, well, if that’s what she [ __ ]
это вообще капец знаешь Ну если она блин
wants  in short, it goes without saying
так хочет короче само собой
now, wait for me something from the
нужно сейчас подожди мне что-то с
Internet
интернета
[laughter] an
[смех]
Armenian from Moscow to a Georgian
армянин из Москвы грузину
Irakli told the whole business scheme
Иракли всю бизнес схему
about both the Russians and Natashik,
рассказал и про русских и про наташик
this video will be a bomb if you
это бомба ролик будет если вы его
watch it Let’s like the squeak Ko and send it to your
смотрите Давайте лайк писка Ко и скиньте
friends Hi stink just the same spoil
друзям Хай вони теж порть
yes  Slava
да Слава
ukraine write on th Telegram directly at the same time
украини пись на й Telegram прям зараз
axis VN
ось ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube keeping
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us busy through skarg Orcs in your ban and even
нас через скарг Орки в твый бан и дуже
more videos I don’t show people constantly don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we Mali operational link
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
write directly at once  Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegrams okrim video schezh tsikava and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
korisna information and we are responsible for you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
subscribe
подпишись а